(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-09T03:04:14.554907",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.7-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
高鳴る心臓に祈りを乗せて
Placing my prayers upon my pounding heart,
曖昧な夢を描く
I paint an ambiguous dream.
幻想は想像のまま
Illusions won't just end
終われないんだ
in imagination alone.
みんな今日はお披露目に来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you so much for coming to the reveal today!
答えを延々と探し続けて
Endlessly searching for answers,
何者かになりたくて
wanting to become someone,
潸々と降る夕立ちを
I merely gazed out
ただ眺めた
at the pouring evening shower.
優しく寄り添って 心が晴れるのなら
If staying gently by your side can clear your heart,
翼が生えたような気がして
I feel as if I've sprouted wings;
いつだって隣にいるから
I'll always be right beside you.
だって言葉紡いで歌うことが わたしの運命だ
Because weaving words into song is my destiny.
世界にありふれた虚しささえも 上書きして
Overwriting even the hollow emptiness of this world,
路地裏に咲いた花のように 願いを照らす
illuminating wishes like a flower blooming in a back alley,
小さな光に憧れて
yearning for that tiny light.
名前を持たない歌なんて 神様は認めてくれない
God won't acknowledge a song without a name.
一つ一つ枯れない花のように
Like flowers that never wither one by one,
昨日の自分にさよならして 零れた涙
saying goodbye to who I was yesterday, tears spill over;
上手く笑えなくてもいいかな
is it okay even if I can't smile properly?
だって理想は遠ざかってくばかり もう散々だよ
Because my ideals keep drifting away, it's just awful.
どれだけ手を伸ばして叫んだって 届かないの
No matter how far I reach and scream, it won't reach.
望めばいつか叶うはずって 信じてる
I believe that if I wish, it will surely come true someday.
どうか歌よ響いて
Please, my song, resound!
あぁ心臓の鼓動が今日も五月蝿い
Ah, the beating of my heart is so loud again today...
行き止まりばっか 足が竦んで 立てないよ
Nothing but dead ends, my legs freeze up and I can't stand.
音のない世界から 君を見つけて 連れ出すんだ
I'll find you in this soundless world and bring you out.
言葉紡いで 歌うことが 私の運命だ
Spinning words and singing is my destiny.
世界にありふれた 虚しささえも 上書きして
Overwriting even the emptiness that overflows in this world.
路地裏に咲いた花のように 願いを照らす
Like a flower blooming in a back alley, illuminating wishes...
小さな光に憧れて
longing for that tiny light.
君の歌姫になれたら
If only I could become your diva...
いいな
that would be wonderful.
okey dokey 返事はいいけど
"Okey dokey"—an answer is fine, but...
冗談なら笑えないよ
if it's a joke, I'm not laughing.
渋滞 曖昧 どっちを向いちゃうの
Congested, ambiguous—which way are you looking?
蜃気楼に手を伸ばした
I reached out to a mirage.
微熱のような夢物語
A slight fever-like fairytale...
そんな光は見ない振りしていた
I pretended not to see that kind of light.
ざわめく鼓動 まだ行かないで
Restless heartbeat, don't leave just yet.
幻じゃ嫌だよ
I don't want it to be an illusion.
私を奪って 魅惑の dancing dancing night
Captivate me on this enchanting dancing, dancing night!
拡がって収まんない universe
An expanding, boundless universe!
君の表情は 私の森羅万象を
Your expression might rewrite...
書き換えちゃうかも 責任重大ね
all of my universe, you have a huge responsibility!
一切合切 dance dance dance we are dancing reed
Through it all, dance dance dance, we are dancing reed!
夢中になって絡み合った ゼログラビティ
Entangled in a trance, zero gravity!
構わず dance dance dance just a dance just a dance
Without a care, dance dance dance, just a dance, just a dance!
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving our voices behind in the darkness,
目を覚ましても離れないで
even if you wake up, don't let go of me.
maybe needy 正気じゃないのよ
Maybe needy, I'm out of my mind.
体温が忘れられない
I can't forget your warmth.
誰彼そんなんじゃないから
It's not just with anyone, so...
独り占めして euphoria
keep me all to yourself, euphoria!
気にしてない様な言葉は装飾で
Words pretending not to care are just decoration,
メイクの様には流せない
they can't be washed away like makeup.
360°偽りだって 隠し切れぬような
Even if it's 360° of deceit, it can't be completely hidden...
私に構って 嬉しいなんて crazy crazy love
Thrilled that you're paying attention to me, crazy, crazy love!
摩天楼から連れさらって
Sweep me away from the skyscrapers!
君の表情は 私の深層心理を
Your expression might substitute...
すり替えちゃうのよ 責任重大ね
my deep subconscious, you have a huge responsibility!
過ぎ去ったネオン 残像 shooting star
Passing neons, an afterimage of a shooting star!
グライダーみたいに漂えば 幸も不幸もなかった
Drifting like a glider, there was neither fortune nor sorrow.
指先でまた君を探している
Reaching out with my fingertips, searching for you again...
その声を聴かせてよ
let me hear your voice!
私に構って 教えてよ恋の先を！
Pay attention to me, tell me what lies beyond love!
拡がって収まんない universe
An expanding, boundless universe!
君の存在は 私の将来までも
Your existence stepped into my future as well,
踏み込んだのよ 付き合ってよね
so stay with me, okay?
一切合切 dance dance dance we are dancing reed
Through it all, dance dance dance, we are dancing reed!
夢中になって絡み合った ゼログラビティ
Entangled in a trance, zero gravity!
構わず dance dance dance just a dance just a dance
Without a care, dance dance dance, just a dance, just a dance!
声は闇に預けたまま
Leaving our voices behind in the darkness,
目を覚ましても離れないで
even if you wake up, don't let go of me.
みんなー！
Everyone!
今日はお誕生日ライブに来てくれて ありがとー！
Thank you so much for coming to my birthday live stream!
コメントも見えてるよー！
I can see your comments too!
最初に聴いてもらったのが『Diva』、『Dancing Reed』でしたー！
The first songs you heard were "Diva" and "Dancing Reed"!
えー、この2つの曲は、あのー、フェスと、
Um, these two songs, well, from the fes,
あと去年のね、ドラマの主題歌に使わせて…使っていただいた曲で、
and as the theme song for last year's drama that I had the privilege to use... that was used for,
すごく思い出に残っているので、最初に2曲歌ってみようかなーと思って選びましたー！
they hold so many memories for me, so I chose them thinking I'd sing these two first!
そして、今回はですね、
And for this time,
ときのそら お披露目誕生日…えー、2026…
Tokino Sora Debut Birthday... um, 2026...
ときのそらおじゃないよ？ ときのそらだよ？
It's not Tokinosorao, okay? It's Tokino Sora!
えー、みんなのつぶやきを待ってるので、たくさんつぶやいてほしいな！
I'm waiting for everyone's tweets, so please tweet a lot!
トレンドに入るといいな！
It'd be great if we trended!
ねえ〜？
Right?
そして、今回のテーマは8周年を象徴する「無限」をモチーフに、
And the theme this time is based on "infinity," symbolizing my 8th anniversary,
宇宙や星をステージに散りばめて、中毒性のあるビート、
scattering space and stars across the stage, with addictive beats
リズムの曲で絡めた、えー、「デジタルパルスライブ」です！
and rhythmic songs intertwined—it's a "Digital Pulse Live"!
デジタルパルスライブです！
It's a Digital Pulse Live!
こちらね、大きな天球が曲によってどう変わるのかを見ていてください。
Please watch how this big celestial sphere here changes with each song.
そしてね、今年のぬんぬんは、えー、5つなので、
And also, this year there are five Nun-nuns,
ぐるぐる回転してます。ぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐるぐる。
so they're spinning around and around. Round and round and round...
そして、よ- 空には、そらザウルスもいるよ。
And up in the sky, Sorasaurus is here too!
そらザウルスはね、なんとね、炎を出せるようになりました。
Sorasaurus can now actually breathe fire!
ぼー！
Whoosh!
あん肝もね、ちゃんとあん肝座もあるんですけど、見えるかな？
And as for Ankimo, there's an Ankimo constellation too. Can you see it?
もちろん、あと今年も新衣装のお披露目や告知したゲストと、
Of course, along with this year's new outfit reveals and announced guests,
えー、あとどんな曲を披露するのかを楽しみに待っててくださいね！
please look forward to what songs we'll be performing!
そして！次に行く前に、
And! Before moving on to the next part,
プチお披露目、最初にしちゃいましょう！
let's do a mini-reveal first!
カメラさん、上を向いてくださーい！
Camera person, please look up!
はーい！というわけで、
Ta-da! So...
新しいクラゲヘア、新髪型お披露目です！
...here's my new jellyfish hairstyle reveal!
それでは早速、ゲストパート行ってみよう！可愛いありがとう！
Now then, let's jump straight to the guest part! Thank you for the "cute"s!
おー、可愛いありがとう！
Oh, thank you for "cute"!
白組さんもいっぱいコメントしてってね！
Siro-gumi, please leave lots of comments too!
最初のゲストは、この人です！
The first guest is... this person!
[GUEST：電脳少女シロ]
[Guest: Dennou Shoujo Siro]
星の降る度に 恋をする度に
Every time a star falls, every time I fall in love,
バイバイ だって 夜はギャラクティカ
Bye-bye, because the night is galactica
[明星ギャラクティカ / 作詞・作曲：ナユタン星人]
[Meisei Galactica / Lyrics & Music: NayutalieN]
今夜は宇宙のアイオライトが いやに眩しいから
Because tonight the iolite of the cosmos is terribly dazzling,
街のネオンから 逃れようか
should we escape from the city neon,
ふたり
just the two of us?
ほどけないくらい揺らぐグラスが 心惑わすから
Because the glass swaying unsteadily bewitches my heart,
あなただけ 今夜だけ
only you, only tonight,
夜に星梯子架ける
we'll cast a ladder of stars into the night
見つめ あなたの表情 照らして 明星ギャラクティカ
Gaze upon and illuminate your expression, morning star galactica
見上げた あなたの瞳が 宇宙が キラキラって光る
Looking up, your eyes—the cosmos—sparkles and shines
近づくほどに 踊って この孤独ごと抱きしめて
The closer we get, dance, and embrace even this loneliness
ふたりの銀河で 手と手が 星と星が
In our galaxy, hand in hand, star to star,
交わって 恋はギャラクティカ
crossing paths, love is galactica
ああ 同じペースで 泳ぎ出すペイヴメント
Ah, swimming out onto the pavement at the same pace
宵と宵で繋ぐ朝へ 一度きりのダンス
Toward the dawn connecting dusk to dusk, a once-in-a-lifetime dance
あなたと私の 灯す星の行方は 何光年先を指した？
Where does the star we light lead, how many light-years ahead did it point?
結ぶオリオンの 愛の星が 真っ赤に燃えるから
Because the love star of Orion we tie together burns bright red,
今夜だけ 踊りましょう
tonight only, let's dance,
夜は天邪鬼だから
because the night is a contrarian
見つめ あなたの表情 隠して 明星ギャラクティカ
Gaze upon and hide your expression, morning star galactica
そのときめいた気持ち踏み散らして 手探りでいいから
Trampling over those fluttering feelings, stumbling in the dark is just fine,
生まれたままの衝動 隠して 明星ギャラクティカ
hide that raw impulse you were born with, morning star galactica
わたしの あなたの 鼓動が ドキドキって疾る
My heartbeat, your heartbeat, racing thump-thump
壊れるほどに 踊るほどに 本当のこと言わないで
To the point of breaking, the more we dance, don't tell me the truth
最後の夜明けは 手と手が 星と星が
At the final dawn, hand in hand, star to star,
ほどけて 君はギャラクティカ
coming undone, you are galactica
いつだって 愛はロマンティカ
Always, love is romantica
パッパッパヤ パッパ パッパ アヤ
Pa-pa-pa-ya, pa-pa, pa-pa, a-ya
はい！というわけで最初のゲストは...
All right! So, our first guest is...
シロちゃんだよ〜！
It's Siro-chan~!
こんにちは！ときのシロで〜す！
Hello! I'm Tokino Siro~!
ときのシロになっちゃった
You turned into Tokino Siro!
本当に今日は、そらちゃんお誕生日おめでとうございます！
Sora-chan, happy birthday to you today!
ありがとう〜！
Thank you~!
すごいね、格好！
That's quite an outfit!
そらちゃんという歌姫にお逢いできると聞いて、出せるものは全部出していこうと思います！
Hearing I'd get to meet a songstress like Sora-chan, I thought I'd show off everything I've got!
そ、そういうことだったんだ
S-So that's what you meant!
待って、これでちゃっ、チャンネルBANしちゃったら...
Wait, what if this gets the cha—channel banned...
そんなことないよ！
That won't happen!
ごめんなさい...
I'm sorry...
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
胸が苦しくなってきました...
My chest is starting to hurt...
大丈夫？
Are you all right?
そらちゃん、クラゲさんには、注射器があると聞きます。
Sora-chan, I hear jellyfish have syringes.
注射器？
Syringes?
毒針を是非、頭でごつんとシロに刺していただけませんか？
Could you please sting Siro with your stinger by headbutting me?
ごつん！
*Bonk!*
うっ、う、うっ...
Ugh, ugh, ugh...
倒れ、倒れちゃう！
You're gonna fall over!
すごい、効いてきました！
Amazing, it's working!
効いてきた？
It's working?
皆さん、そらちゃんは変わりました。毒針を持った女に変わったんです！
Everyone, Sora-chan has changed. She's turned into a woman with a poison stinger!
そう、私強くなったから！
That's right, because I got stronger!
そらちゃんは毒針を持ちたくて、可愛いクラゲヘアになったんですか？
Did you get that cute jellyfish hair because you wanted a stinger, Sora-chan?
いやいやいや、私やっぱりアイドルといえばこういう可愛い髪型の人が多いかな〜と思って
No, no, no! I just thought lots of idols have this kind of cute hairstyle,
そういうアイドルっぽい髪型にしたいなと思ってたんだよね〜
so I wanted to try a classic idol hairstyle like this~
はぁ〜そらちゃんって、聞いてください。
*Sigh* Sora-chan, listen to this.
なになに？
What is it?
もうアイドルでしかないし、歌姫でしかないのに、「Diva」っていう曲もですけど、
You're already the epitome of an idol and a songstress, like in your song "Diva,"
今もアイドルであろうとこう、なんか...なってるもんね。
yet even now, you're constantly striving to be the best idol you can be.
努力してくれる姿がもう大好きで、食べたいくらい！
I love seeing how hard you work, I could just eat you up!
食べちゃうの？
You're gonna eat me?
シナモンロールみたいですね。
You look like a cinnamon roll.
見て、カメラさん、見て見て！
Look, camera-san, look, look!
う〜ん
Mmh~
これはシナモンロール！
This is definitely a cinnamon roll!
シナモン...あ、食べられてる、食べられてる！
Cinna... Ah, I'm being eaten, I'm being eaten!
いい匂い...
Smells so nice...
食べられてる〜！
I'm being eaten~!
はい！ということで、今日はBANしない発言を心がけていきます！
All right! So today, I'll make sure not to say anything that gets us banned!
もうすでに結構シロちゃんワールド炸裂してますけど...
You've already unleashed the Siro-chan World in full force, though...
あの、なんかこんな大好きなそらちゃんのこんな場に、
Um, I never imagined that I'd be invited to such a wonderful place...
そらともの皆さんと一緒に呼んでもらえると思わなくて...
...together with all the Soratomo, for my beloved Sora-chan...
ね、3年ぶりだよ！
Yeah, it's been three years!
3年ぶりの元カノです！
It's your ex-girlfriend after three years!
元カノじゃない！
Not ex-girlfriend!
そらともさん、一緒に、一緒に、
Soratomo, let's together, together...
独り占めしないので愛でていきましょう！
...I won't keep her to myself, so let's cherish her together!
今日はそらともさんに、シロの来た意味を分からせたいと思います。
Today, I want to show all the Soratomo the meaning behind Siro coming here.
そらちゃん、立ってください。
Sora-chan, please stand up.
はい！
Okay!
3、2、1、バニーガールで...
3, 2, 1, bunny girl...
この服装でいいの？ねぇ？
Is this outfit really okay? Huh?
千手観音
Thousand-Armed Kannon!
そらちゃん新衣装のバニー衣装プレゼントしに来ました！
I came to present Sora-chan's new bunny costume!
ありがとう〜！
Thank you~!
どうですか？
How is it?
可愛いよ、バニーガールも可愛いよ！
It's cute! The bunny girl is cute too!
ウサギさんって万年発情してるので、ちょっとハーハーしてもら...
Rabbits are in heat all year round, so could you pant a little—
こら！
Hey!
かわいい〜！
So cute~!
私も尻尾あるよ！
I have a tail too!
そうだよ！そらちゃんと言えば...
That's right! Speaking of Sora-chan...
尻尾は...ちょ、ちょっと...押してもいいですか？
May I... j-just poke your tail?
いいよ、ツンツン
Sure, poke away!
大変！
Oh no!
何？
What?
シロ、発情が止まらないので...
Siro can't stop being in heat, so...
やばい！
Oh no!
そろそろお家に帰ります！
I'm heading home now!
帰っちゃうの？
You're leaving already?
はい！月から皆を見守っています。この後も楽しんで〜！
Yes! I'll watch over everyone from the moon. Enjoy the rest of the show~!
楽しむよ〜！ありがとう〜！
We will~! Thank you~!
本当に...あ、なんか出てきた...
Really... Ah, something's sticking out...
ちょっと、帰れてないよ〜！
Wait, you haven't left properly~!
シロちゃんワールド炸裂で楽しかったね！
The Siro-chan World was in full swing, that was so fun!
「何だこれ」って言わないで、みんな！ねぇ〜
Don't say "What was that?!", everyone! Come on~
けど、相変わらずのシロちゃんで、私、一緒に歌えてとっても楽しかったです！
But Siro-chan was as delightful as ever, and I had so much fun singing together!
マイペースだね。ね、マイペースだよ！
She does things at her own pace. Right at her own pace!
私もマイペースだから、いいコンビってことだ！
I'm also easygoing, so we make a great duo!
というわけで、続いてのゲストに行きましょう！この人です！
And with that, let's move on to the next guest! Here she is!
[GUEST 緋月ゆい]
[Guest: Hizuki Yui]
全部全部アンタのせいだ
It's all, all your fault.
反吐が出るくらいにウザったいわ
You're so annoying it makes me want to throw up.
何かに縋って諂って
Clinging to something, flattering someone,
期待したアタシが馬鹿だった
I was a fool to have had expectations.
ご機嫌伺いの八方美人
A people-pleaser trying to butter everyone up,
それ故にアンチな一生 gimme
so give me a lifetime of hate.
浅いキャパシティ まいどおおきに
A shallow capacity, thank you very much.
詰まるとこ人生ずっと地味
In the end, my life has always been plain.
「憎たらしい！」「痛々しい！」
"How hateful!" "How pathetic!"
無視出来ないのが一層 腹立たしい 苛立たしい
The fact that I can't ignore it makes it even more infuriating and irritating.
そろそろ飽きた 自画自賛に
I've had just about enough of your self-praise.
ライクの反対はアパシー
The opposite of like is apathy,
≒繋がれた証
≒ proof of being connected.
切り離せない関係
A relationship that can't be severed,
逸らしてしまいたいわ
I just want to look away.
これは所謂ヘイトスピーチ
This is what they call hate speech.
匿名性の声明を生命に乗せてんだ
Carrying an anonymous declaration on life itself.
鳴り止まないサイレン 近づく度に痙攣
Endless sirens, spasming every time they draw near.
赤信号にずっと従順です
Always obedient to the red light.
大体 アナタのコト アタシ
Basically, as for you, I...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライ
hate hate hate hate hate you!
omg 情けない もはや
OMG, how pathetic, I want to say...
バイバイバイ バイバイ したい
bye bye bye bye bye already.
脳内も予測不能故に
Inside the brain is unpredictable, too, so...
解 解 解 解解は無い
there is no no no no no answer.
どうだい？ アタシのコト アナタ
How about it? As for me, did you...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライになった？
come to hate hate hate hate hate me?
あぁ 百害あって一利ナシ nothing not see
Ah, all harm and no benefit, nothing not see.
もしタラレバ並べても ニコチンだし
Even if I line up "what-ifs," it's just nicotine.
i miss youって近づいた 結末は凡ミス 凡ミス
I came close saying "I miss you," but the result was a simple blunder, simple blunder.
センキュー反面教師
Thank you, negative role model.
後味一生消えてくんないわ
The aftertaste won't fade away for the rest of my life.
よしよし いい子ね
There, there, good girl.
笑顔振り撒き パラパラ いい子ね
Scattering smiles all around, what a good girl.
だけど だけど その本性は？
But, but, what is your true nature?
善悪の区別も付かないの？笑 はぁ。
Can't even tell right from wrong? (Laughs) *Sigh*.
減点方式で取り巻く環境に巻かれて
Caught in an environment governed by a deduction system,
生涯「痛い！痛い！痛い！も聞かれないわ！」って
crying all your life, "No one will listen to my pain!"
当然の報いに喰らっちゃった
You were struck by natural retribution.
人は鏡なんです
People are mirrors.
実のところ依存は両辺です
In reality, dependency goes both ways.
シャットダウンしても付き纏う
Even if I shut it down, it clings to me.
己の弱さが不甲斐ない
My own weakness is so pathetic.
全部全部アンタのせいで
It's all, all because of you,
反吐が出るくらいに止まんないわ
it won't stop to the point of throwing up.
いっその事 切り離せた方が楽なのに… なぁ
It would be so much easier if I could just sever it... right?
大体 アナタのコト アタシ
Basically, as for you, I...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライ
hate hate hate hate hate you!
omg 情けない もはや
OMG, how pathetic, I want to say...
バイバイバイ バイバイ したい
bye bye bye bye bye already.
脳内も予測不能故に
Inside the brain is unpredictable, too, so...
解 解 解 解解は無い
there is no no no no no answer.
どうだい？ アタシのコト アナタ
How about it? As for me, did you...
ダイダイ ダイダイ ダイ キライになった？
come to hate hate hate hate hate me?
あぁ 百害あって一利ナシ nothing not see
Ah, all harm and no benefit, nothing not see.
もしタラレバ並べても ニコチンだし
Even if I line up "what-ifs," it's just nicotine.
i miss youって近づいた 結末は凡ミス 凡ミス
I came close saying "I miss you," but the result was a simple blunder, simple blunder.
センキュー反面教師
Thank you, negative role model.
後味一生消えてくんないわ
The aftertaste won't fade away for the rest of my life.
イエーイ！
Yay!
どうもー！
Hello!
というわけで、ゲストは…
And so, our guest is...
ゆいちゃんでーす！
Yui-chan!
はい！改めましてNeo-Porte所属の緋月ゆいです！
Yes! Once again, I'm Hiizuki Yui from Neo-Porte!
そらさん、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Sora-san, happy birthday!
ありがとー！来てくれて嬉しい！
Thank you! I'm so happy you came!
おめでとー！
Congrats!
去年ぶりー！
First time since last year!
去年ぶり！
Since last year!
いやーね、去年はね、
Yeah, you know, last year...
はい。
Yes.
ちょっと残念ながら、
unfortunately,
はい。
yes,
メッセージだけということで…
it was just a message, so...
あの、去年は本当に申し訳なかったです…
Um, I'm really sorry about last year...
なんで！謝らないでー！
Why! Don't apologize!
いや、もうメッセージでもね、すごくみんな「うおお！」ってなってて、
No, even with the message, everyone went "Whoa!",
嬉しかったですよ！
and I was so happy!
すごいガラガラ声でね、去年は…
With a really raspy voice last year...
参加させていただいたんですけども、
I joined in, but...
今年はリベンジができてとっても嬉しいです！
I'm so happy I was able to get my revenge this year!
やったー！リベンジだー！
Yay! It's revenge!
呼んでいただいて嬉しいです。ありがとうございます！
I'm so glad you invited me. Thank you so much!
こちらこそー！
The pleasure is mine!
今回の曲もね、私が選んだんですけども、
I chose this song as well, but...
やっぱり、あの、ゆいちゃんといえばかっこいい声、
after all, when it comes to Yui-chan, having a cool voice...
っていうのがね、すごく私の中で…
is something that was strongly in my mind...
えー！嬉しいです！
Wow! That makes me so happy!
もう頭の中にあって。いや、かっこいいよ！
It was in my head. Really, you're so cool!
なので、このね、デュエットっていうのもあるので、
So, since this is a duet,
この曲を是非一緒に歌いたいと思って！
I really wanted to sing this song together with you!
嬉しい！ありがとうございます！
I'm so glad! Thank you so much!
どうだったかな？
How was it?
いや、あの、歌も超難しかったんですけど、
Well, um, the singing was super difficult, but...
どちらかというとダンスが、普段あんまりしないので…
if anything, the dancing... since I don't usually dance much...
そうだよね！
That's true!
はい、ちょっとこそこそとダンスレッスンなどをね…
Yes, so I secretly took dance lessons and such...
え、レッスンしたの？！
Eh, you took lessons?!
やらさせていただきましてですね、本番に向けて…
I took them, and toward the actual show...
ね まさかね ダンスまでしてくれると思わなかったの
I really didn't think you'd even dance with me!
え、本当ですか？
Eh, really?
誘った時に「ダンスもあるんですけど…」って言った時に
When I invited you and said, "There's also dancing involved, though..."
はい
Yes.
「やだ」ってなるかなと思ったから
I thought you might say, "No thanks."
ぜひ！と思いました
I thought, "Definitely!"
本当に？
Really?
普段ね、こう右…右手でどうにかしてるんで
Usually, I just manage somehow with my right hand,
手持ちマイクで右手でどうにか尺稼ぎしてたんですけど
trying to fill time with my right hand holding the mic,
今日はダンスに挑戦できたのが自分的にもすごい嬉しかったです
so I was really happy that I got to try dancing today!
めちゃめちゃかっこよかった！
You looked so, so cool!
いやいや、一緒に踊れて超嬉しかったんで
No, no, I was super happy to dance together with you!
私も嬉しかった！
I was so happy too!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
こちらこそー！
Thank you as well!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
どうだったー？
How did you like it?
かっこよかったでしょ？
She was so cool, right?
頑張ったぞー！
We did our best!
頑張ったよー！
We sure did!
はい
Yes.
という感じで、このあともね、まだライブがあるということなので
So with that, there's still more of the live show to come,
はい！
Yes!
このあともぜひ頑張ってください！
so please give it your all for the rest of it!
頑張るよー！
I'll do my best!
応援してます！
I'm rooting for you!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
はい、ということで、ネオポルテの緋月ゆいでした！ありがとうございました！
Yes! So, I was Hizuki Yui from Neo-Porte! Thank you so much!
緋月ちゃんでしたー！
That was Hizuki-chan!
頑張ってねー！
Good luck!
ありがとねー！
Thank you!
ばいばーい！
Bye-bye!
てぃおー！
Tio!
えー、ということで、緋月ちゃんが来てくれました！緋月ちゃんって言ったの初めてかも(笑)
And so, Hizuki-chan came on stage! That might be my first time calling her Hizuki-chan, haha.
ゆいちゃんが来てくれました！嬉しいねー！
Yui-chan came by! I'm so happy!
というわけで、あっという間なんだけど、私、口癖「と」…「というわけで」なんだな、今気づいちゃった(笑)
And so, it's gone by in a flash... Ah, "and so" is my verbal tic, I just realized that, haha.
ここからライブ後半戦です！
From here on, it's the second half of the live show!
それでは、5曲目聴いてください。
Now then, please listen to song number five.
モニタリング
"Monitoring"
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人涙してんの知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know that you're shedding tears all alone.
ビクンビクン震えてさ 声もダダ漏れなんだわ
Shivering and shaking, your voice is leaking out completely.
正直に言っちゃえば バレてるんだし言っちゃえば
Why not just be honest? It's already obvious anyway.
聞いてんの？
Are you listening?
普通 普通 平気だよ みんな分かってないだけ むふっ
It's normal, totally normal. Everyone else just doesn't get it. *snicker*
もしもし？ねぇ、大丈夫？
Hello? Hey, are you okay?
うん、心配だから今からそっち行くね。
Yeah, I'm worried about you, so I'm heading over right now.
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人涙してんの知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know that you're shedding tears all alone.
グスングスンへこんでさ 弱音ヒトカラいいんじゃない？
Sniffling and feeling down, solo karaoke to vent sounds good, doesn't it?
朝が来るまで一緒コース もっと泣いたって
We're staying together until morning comes, so go ahead and cry more.
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept all of it, over and over again.
もう我慢しないで いっぱい吐いてね
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out, okay?
むーわ！お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
慰めさせて Best Friend 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, Best Friend, with my talent for love.
泣いてくれるかい？
Will you cry for me?
君の辛い抱きしめたい
I want to embrace all your pain.
ねぇいいでしょ？
Hey, won't you let me?
分け合って乗り越えたいんだ ったったってば
I want to share it and overcome it together, I'm telling you!
むーわ！お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
笑い飛ばして ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ さあ行こうぜ
Laugh it off with a hop, step, jump, come on, let's go!
分けてくれるかい？
Will you share it with me?
君に重い暗い病み 想い
That heavy, dark darkness weighing on you, those feelings.
ねぇいいでしょ？
Hey, won't you let me?
寄り添って救いたいんだ ったったってば
I want to stay close and save you, I'm telling you!
見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい
I wanna see, wanna see, wanna see, wanna see...
見たい 見たいの 君の中
I wanna see, wanna see inside of you.
見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい 見たい
I wanna see, wanna see, wanna see, wanna see...
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人悔しがってんの知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know that you're feeling frustrated all alone.
グスングスン終わるまで 君を決して諦めない
Until all your sniffling stops, I will never give up on you.
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ 君はできる子 知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're capable.
辛い時は弱いくらいで丁度いい あたし君の味方だよ
When it's tough, being a little weak is just right; I'm always on your side.
むーわ！お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
名前を呼んでよ いつだって愛に参上
Call my name, and I'll always arrive with love!
君は一人かい？
Are you alone?
それは違う 一人じゃない
That's not true, you're not alone!
もういいでしょ？
Isn't that enough already?
ソロプレイはおしまいなんだ ったったってば
Your solo play is over, I'm telling you!
君がどんなときも
No matter what kind of times you face,
あたしそばにいるわ
I'll always be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ
I'll always be watching over you.
そうよ怖くないのよ
That's right, there's nothing to be afraid of.
ほー、ほー、ほー
Ooh, ooh, ooh...
むーわ！お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
慰めさせて Best Friend 愛の才能で
Let me comfort you, Best Friend, with my talent for love.
泣いてくれるかい？
Will you cry for me?
君の辛い抱きしめたい
I want to embrace all your pain.
ねぇいいでしょ？
Hey, won't you let me?
分け合って乗り越えたいんだ ったったってば
I want to share it and overcome it together, I'm telling you!
むーわ！お願い 君が欲しいの
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad.
笑い飛ばして ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ さあ行こうぜ
Laugh it off with a hop, step, jump, come on, let's go!
分けてくれるかい？
Will you share it with me?
君に重い暗い病み 想い 覗きたい
That heavy, dark darkness weighing on you, those feelings, I want to peek inside.
吸い取って救いたいんだ ったったってば
I want to absorb it and save you, I'm telling you!
ねぇ あたし知ってるよ 君が一人涙してんの知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know that you're shedding tears all alone.
グスングスンへこんでさ 弱音ヒトカラいいんじゃない？
Sniffling and feeling down, solo karaoke to vent sounds good, doesn't it?
ずっと一緒 もう泣いたって 何度だって受け止めてあげる
We're together forever, so even if you cry more, I'll accept it all again and again.
もう我慢しないで 出してってってってばー！
Don't hold back anymore, let it all out, I'm telling you!
はーい！ということで、新衣装でーす！
Alright! And with that, here is my new outfit!
みんな可愛い？(笑)
Isn't it cute, everyone? haha
気になるとは思うけど、紹介は後で！
I know you're curious, but I'll introduce it in detail later!
先にゲストの方と歌うよ！
First, I'm going to sing with my next guest!
どうぞー！
Come on out!
僕らよ 始まれ
May we begin,
Awalk Awalk 果てまで
Awalk Awalk, to the very end.
繭の裂け目を開けた Birthday 芳しく煮えられそうな Birthday
A birthday breaking through the cocoon, a birthday that feels pleasantly scorched.
どこに居てて足りない 命はひとつずつ足りない Yeah
Wherever I am, it's not enough; one life at a time isn't enough, yeah.
羽ばたくのは何故 (まだ)
Why do we take flight? (Not yet)
風邪引きな夢を見る (笑わないで まだ)
I dream feverish dreams. (Don't laugh just yet)
ふたりなら (ふたりなら)
If it's the two of us, (if it's the two of us,)
どこまでも行けると どうしてか信じたくなって
somehow I just want to believe we can go anywhere.
跳ねる鼓動 誰を呼ぶのベルの音 どうして待っての瞬間 春夏秋冬 我が儘プッシュダウ
A bouncing pulse, a ringing bell calling someone, moments pleading to wait, seasons passing, selfishly pushing down.
あっという間に終わる 祭りの合図 恐れさえも笑い合おう
A signal of a festival over in a flash, let's laugh off even our fears together.
共に Hello
Together, hello,
歌って！
sing out!
不完全体 ゆえに面白くなってきた
An incomplete state, that's what makes it fun now.
空腹の夜を越え 空白に願い唱え
Crossing through hungry nights, chanting wishes into the void,
諦め尽くされた世界を 君とふたり 地面に転げ回り
through a world given up on, rolling around on the ground together with you,
混ざり合い そして生まれ変わるような
blending together, as if being reborn,
きっと僕らだけが出せるパレード
surely this is a parade that only we can bring to life.
絶対証明したい新火災 最高潮 叫んだ 正体？疾走したい 密造次第
A new blaze we must prove, shouted at its peak, our true form? Wanting to sprint, depending on what we forge,
(隣同士で？)
(side by side?)
架空も現実も全部 敷き詰めたがり 過去の惜別を煮て語ればかり
Wanting to pave over both fiction and reality, only dwelling on past farewells.
今はそこに君がいる 未知なるバージョン 確定で Yeah
Now, you are right there, confirmed as an unknown new version, yeah.
名も無きヒーロー
A nameless hero,
Ah ah
行こうか
let's go!
僕らよ 始まれ
May we begin,
Awalk Awalk 果てまで
Awalk Awalk, to the very end.
歌って！
Sing out!
不完全体 ゆえに面白くなってきた
An incomplete state, that's what makes it fun now.
空腹の夜を越え 空白に願い唱え
Crossing through hungry nights, chanting wishes into the void,
諦め尽くされた世界を 君とふたり 地面に転げ回り
through a world given up on, rolling around on the ground together with you,
混ざり合い そして生まれ変わるような
blending together, as if being reborn,
きっと僕らこそが出せるパレード
surely this is a parade that only we could bring to life.
Yeah yeah yeah
La la la la la la la la Yeah
完全体 突き抜くパレード
A parade breaking through in our complete form.
はーい！というわけで！ / はい！
Alright! So with that! / Yes!
ゲストの前にちょっとね、先ほどね / そうですね
Before introducing our guest, just a moment ago... / That's right.
東北の方で地震があったみたいですが、大丈夫でしょうか？
it seems there was an earthquake in Tohoku. Is everyone alright?
東北の方、身の回りの安全を優先でお願いします！
To everyone in Tohoku, please prioritize your safety above all!
気をつけるんだよー！
Stay safe out there!
気をつけてください！
Please stay safe!
そして！次のゲストはリオナちゃんでーす！
And now! Our guest is Riona-chan!
はーい！FLOW GLOWのリーダー、響咲リオナです！
Hello! I'm FLOW GLOW's leader, Hibiki Riona!
ぶるらっぱー！よろしくお願いしまーす！イエーイ！
Blurapper! So happy to be here! Yay!
そして、そら先輩、お誕生日おめでとうございます！
And Sora-senpai, happy birthday!
ありがとうございますー！嬉しいー！ / ございます！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy! / Congrats!
今日はね、最近めちゃくちゃ仲が良いっていうのと、やっぱ…
Today, partly because we've gotten super close recently, and...
めっちゃ仲良いですもんね！ / ねえ！仲良い！
We really get along so well! / Right! Super close!
あと歌とダンスといえば、なんか今はリオナちゃんってイメージがあって
And when it comes to singing and dancing, Riona-chan instantly comes to mind,
えー！嬉しい！
Aw! That makes me so happy!
なんか一緒にね、歌いたいと思って呼んじゃいました！
so I really wanted to sing together with you, and invited you here!
えー！本当に嬉しかったです、呼んでもらえた時！
Aw! I was honestly so thrilled when you invited me!
それよりそれより！そら先輩！ / はいはい。何ですか？
More importantly, Sora-senpai! / Yes, yes. What is it?
新衣装じゃないですか！ / そうなんです！
Isn't that a brand new outfit?! / It sure is!
めちゃくちゃ可愛い！
It's so ridiculously cute!
ありがとうございまーす！
Thank you so much!
どんな衣装なんですか？
What kind of outfit is it?
こちらはですね、去年出したアルバムの『Pulse』っていうジャケットで
This is, well, from the cover of the album "Pulse" that I released last year,
着てた衣装なんですけど
the outfit I wore on it,
もう実際にライブでも着たいと思って仕立てて…
and I wanted to actually wear it live, so I had it tailored...
いただきましたー！
Thank you very much!
あら、もうそんな、そらともさんも「ぎゅーっ」て感じ？
Oh my, are the Soratomo feeling all warm and squeezy too?
いいえ、カチンコチンになっちゃうかもしれない。
No, they might actually freeze stiff!
じゃあ、あの、シロさんを見習って、
Well then, following Shiro-san's lead,
リオナが来た意味をね、今から私もやっていこうと思うんですけど、
I'd like to fulfill the purpose of my coming here too...
おっ、何ですか？
Oh, what is it?
まあ、みんなもね、写真がいっぱい撮りたいと思いますので、
Well, I'm sure everyone wants to take lots of photos,
あ、そうですね。
Ah, right.
リオナ直伝のセクシーポーズ写真！
Photos of sexy poses taught directly by Riona!
おっ。
Ooh.
どうですか？
How about it?
やるやるー！
Let's do it, let's do it!
スクショ大会！
A screenshot contest!
大会？
A contest?
大会です、もうこれは。
It's totally a contest now.
大会だった。
It's a contest now.
あの、セクシーなポーズを直伝…直伝？
So I'll teach you sexy poses directly... directly?
直伝！伝授してくれるのね？
Directly! You'll pass them down to me?
伝授するのね！
Pass them down, yes!
それをね、そらともさんに写真撮ってもらうという回で。もう私はあの、もう画面外で…
It's a session for Soratomo to take photos. As for me, I'll just step off-screen...
え、なんで？
Eh, why?
後で一緒に撮ろうね。
Let's take some together later, okay?
あ、オッケーです。
Ah, okay!
じゃあ、まず…
Well then, first...
やっぱリオナと言えばこれ。リオナと言えば、まあこれですから。
When it comes to Riona, it's gotta be this. This is Riona's signature, after all.
これできるかな、私…
I wonder if I can pull this off...
これはちょっと、ちょっと足をこう…
For this, kind of spread your legs like...
私的にはちょっと…
For me, that's a bit...
ちょっ…色々アウト！色々…
Wait... That's pretty risky in various ways!
こういうのはどうですか？こういうの。
How about something like this? Like this.
そういうのね！
Like that, right!
もうリオナはね、行きますからどっか。
Riona will just get out of the way over here.
あーいいですね！いいですね！あーいいです！
Ah, that's great! That's great! Ah, looking good!
ちょっと右手を前に出しちゃったりしてー
Maybe extend your right hand forward a bit...
あ、いいですね！いいですね！
Ah, nice! Looking great!
あーちょっと、あーいい！うまい！
Ah, wait... Ah, perfect! Well done!
あれ？そら先輩、セクシーの才能がかなりあるんじゃないですか？
Wait? Sora-senpai, don't you have quite the talent for being sexy?
おおー！素晴らしい！
Ooh! Wonderful!
え、あとはどうしようかな…
Um, what should I do next...
ちょっ…あ、嫌だ！いいの！？そのポーズ！
Wait... Ah, no way! Is that pose okay?!
そういう事じゃないの？セクシーって。
Isn't that what sexy is about?
ま、ちょっと教える必要なかったですよ、これー。
Well, there was totally no need for me to teach you this!
うわ、うま…ちょっ、あ、ちょっと！うわ、後ろからのアングルめっちゃいいな。
Whoa, so good... Wait, ah, hold on! Whoa, the angle from behind is amazing.
ちょっと！恥ずかしがらせないでよ！
Hey! Don't embarrass me!
あの、なんかね、こ、こういうのとかね。やっほーみたいな。
Um, like, th-this kind of pose too. Like "Yoo-hoo!"
後ろからのー、イェーイ！
From behind—yay!
あ、いいですね！いいですね！かわいい！色とりどりでめっちゃ綺麗ですね。
Ah, that's great! That's great! Cute! It's so colorful and pretty.
そう、なの。グラデーションが入ってて可愛いんだよー。
Right? The gradient makes it so cute!
めっちゃ可愛い！
Super cute!
え、じゃあ一緒に写ってくれますか？
Um, then will you pose with me?
もちろんですよー！
Of course!
そらりおポーズ、考えようって言ってたのに全然考えられなかった。
We talked about coming up with a Sora-Rio pose, but we couldn't think of one at all.
なんかね、クマとなんかリオナっぽいポーズが…あとなんかリオナの公式ポーズがこれなんですけど、
Like, a bear and a Riona-ish pose... Also, Riona's official pose is this one, but...
私はこうなんだよね。
Mine is like this.
そう、だからそしたらなんか…
Yeah, so if we do that, kinda...
ほぼ似てる、みたいな。ほぼ一緒。
They're almost identical. Almost the same.
そしたらクマ、クマと手当てる？こう？あ、これが…
Then the bear... bear and extending hands? Like this? Ah, this...
これがいいんじゃないかって思ってるんですけど、皆さんどうですか？
I was thinking this might be good, what does everyone think?
どうですか？
How is it?
そらりおポーズ。
The Sora-Rio pose.
クマとのばし。
Bear and stretch.
あん肝とのばし。
Ankimo and stretch.
え、あとあれですよ。最近私のこと飲んでるって本当ですか？
Oh, and by the way: is it true you've been drinking me recently?
そう！リオナ茶を。貧血のリオナ茶を。すごく助かっています！
Yes! Riona tea. The Riona tea for anemia. It's been helping me so much!
あ、本当ですか？じゃあもういつでも呼び出してください。リオナ吸われに行くんで。
Ah, really? Then feel free to summon me anytime. Riona will come over to get drained!
あ、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you very much.
そら先輩どうぞーって。
Saying, "Help yourself, Sora-senpai!"
うわーーー！
Whoaaa!
助かる！私が助かる！
That helps! That helps me so much!
いつでもね、あの、補給しますんで。
I can resupply you anytime.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
いつでも呼んでくださいね！
Please call me anytime!
はーい！
Okaay!
あれ？お、おいっ…
Huh? H-Hey...
リオナちゃん！？
Riona-chan?!
ちょ、そら…そら先輩助けて！そら先輩！
Wai... Sora... Sora-senpai, help! Sora-senpai!
リオナちゃん！リオナちゃん！
Riona-chan! Riona-chan!
そら先輩！あーーー！
Sora-senpai! Aaaah!
あははは、パンツ…
Hahaha, panties...
こら！みんな、みんなそれをやっていくんだ！
Hey! Everyone, is everyone going to do that?!
みんなそれをやっていくんだ…
Everyone's going to end up doing that...
さあー、でもねリオナちゃんともね、本当に仲が良くて、
Now then, but you know, I get along really well with Riona-chan,
いつもね、よく会うんですけど、
and we meet up often, but...
普段と変わらない、Kawaii感じでしたね。
she was her usual cute self, wasn't she?
私が消えましたね、ごめんなさい。
I disappeared for a second, sorry about that.
お水を飲みにいっていました。はい！
I went to drink some water. Yep!
というわけで、
And so,
続いてのゲストは、もう誰だか分かるよね？
for our next guest, you already know who it is, right?
この人です！
It's this person!
GUEST 風真いろは
[Guest: Kazama Iroha]
ヒビカセ / 作詞: Reol 作曲: Giga
[Hibikase / Lyrics: Reol, Music: Giga]
真夜中に告ぐ 音の警告
A warning of sound told in the middle of the night,
協和音に酔う 午前零時
intoxicated by consonance at midnight.
あなたが触れる 光増す熱
You touch me, the heat increases,
指先に踊らされ
dancing at your fingertips.
感覚 即 体感
Sensation, instant bodily sensation.
寝静まる夜 二人だけの密
A quiet night, a secret just for the two of us.
体感 即 快感
Bodily sensation, instant pleasure.
重なる波形に魅了されていく
Fascinated by the overlapping waveforms.
忘れないでね 私の声を
Please don't forget my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
Even through a screen is fine, love me properly
ヴァーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Just because I'm virtual, don't push me away
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね 私の声を
Please remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
Everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
Gazing at each other, just the two of us
重ねた息と 音とヒビカセ
Let our overlapping breaths and sounds resonate
真夜中に問う 冷え切った熱
Asking in the dead of night, a heat turned cold
待ち続けてる 午前0時
Continuing to wait at midnight
鏡写しに 飽和していく
Saturating in the mirror's reflection
知らない音が伝う
An unfamiliar sound travels through
感覚 即 体感
Sensation, instantly experienced
寝静まる夜と 息遣い揃う
The quiet night aligns with our breathing
体感 即 快感
Experience, instantly pleasure
錆びたロジック 今一度を焦がれる
Rusted logic yearns for "one more time"
忘れないでね 私の声を
Please don't forget my voice
次元も超えて 飛ばすシグナル
A signal sent beyond dimensions
ヴァーチャルだなんて 言わないで
Don't call me merely virtual
あなたの音に まだ愛されていたい
I still want to be loved by your sound
覚えていてね 私の声を
Please remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
Everything of this body you gave me
言の葉と 初の音が交わる
Words and the very first sound intertwine
この息と音と ヒビカセ
Let this breath and sound resonate
ああ あなたの生んだ音に
Ah, with the sounds you gave birth to,
ああ ただ恋をしていたの
Ah, I was simply in love
悲しみ 怒り 歓心 すべて 打ち鳴らす
Sorrow, anger, delight—ringing them all out
絶えず叫ぶ 声連ねる
Constantly shouting, connecting voices
余熱混ぜる 愛絶つ艶めく
Mixing lingering heat, cutting love, blooming allure
絶えず叫ぶ 声連ねる
Constantly shouting, connecting voices
余熱混ぜる 愛絶つ艶めく
Mixing lingering heat, cutting love, blooming allure
魅了されていく
Becoming enchanted
忘れないでね 私の声を
Please don't forget my voice
画面越しでいい ちゃんと愛して
Even through a screen is fine, love me properly
ヴァーチャルだって 突き放さないで
Just because I'm virtual, don't push me away
あなたの音に まだ溺れていたい
I still want to drown in your sound
覚えていてね 私の声を
Please remember my voice
あなたがくれた この身すべてを
Everything of this body you gave me
見つめ合う あなたと二人
Gazing at each other, just the two of us
重ねた息と 音を響かせ
Let our overlapping breaths and sounds resonate
あなたの初音 この声聴かせ
Your first sound, let this voice be heard
オトヒビカセ
Let the sound resonate
はーい！というわけで最後のゲストは、いろはちゃんでーす！
All right! And our final guest is Iroha-chan!
いぇーい！ホロックスの、強い、イケメン、速い、かっこいい、んーなんかすごい、風真いろはでーす！
Yay! HoloX's strong, handsome, fast, cool, um, kind of amazing Kazama Iroha de gozaru!
いぇーい！
Yay!
おかしいな...
That's strange...
おかしいな？
Strange?
そら先輩。
Sora-senpai.
なに？
What is it?
お誕生日おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
おかしいな...
That's strange...
何がおかしいんだい？
What's strange?
リハーサル日まではあんなにメロついてくれてたのに...
Up until rehearsal day, you were swooning over me so much...
すごいじゃん！今日、今日のために整えてくれたってこと？
That's amazing! You mean you pulled yourself together just for today?
今日のために、ちょっとあの整えさせていただきました。
Just for today, I made sure to pull myself together.
いやぁ、ありがとうございます！
Wow, thank you!
コメント欄のみんなもあんなにメロついてくれてたのに、今日は全然メロついてない！
Everyone in the comments was swooning like crazy too, but today they're not swooning at all!
いやいや、そんなことなかったよ。「かっこいい、2人とも」って書いてあったよ！
No, no, that's not true. They were writing, "Both of you are so cool!"
え、本当ですか？
Wait, really?
本当に！
Really!
え、ちょっともう一回見たいから「かっこいい」って書いてもらって...
Um, I want to see it again, so could you write "cool"...
「かっこいい」って！みんな「かっこいい」って書いて！
"Cool"! Everyone, write "cool"!
「かわいい」「かわいい」「かわいい」... かわいい？
"Cute," "cute," "cute"... Cute?
かわいいのは当たり前じゃん！
Being cute is a given!
あ、あ、そうだよ...そうそうですね。
Ah, right... Yeah, that's true.
ござるちゃんはいつでもかわいい！
Gozaru-chan is always cute!
ほら、「かっこいい」「かっこいい」って！
Look, they're saying "cool, cool"!
あ、ありがと...ありがとうございます！言わせて「かっこいい」が義務だとしても、風真いろはは嬉しいぞ！
Th-thank... Thank you so much! Even if saying "cool" was out of obligation, Kazama Iroha is still happy!
ね、あの1人でもね、記念配信で歌ってたけど、すごく似合ってたから一緒に歌いたいなと思って、呼んじゃいました！
You know, you sang it on your anniversary stream, but it suited you so well that I wanted to sing it together, so I invited you!
嬉しいー！
I'm so happy!
嬉しくってー！嬉しくって死んでしまう！
I'm so happy! I'm so happy I could die!
生きて！生きて！
Live! Stay alive!
あ、生きてますよ！生きてます！
Ah, I'm alive! I'm alive!
おー、よかったよかった！
Oh, thank goodness!
いや、でも神曲！やっぱそら先輩といえばボカロめっちゃ似合うなーって、ずっと思ってたんで...
But really, what a god-tier song! When it comes to Sora-senpai, Vocaloid songs suit you so well, which I've always thought...
本当？
Really?
「いつかやってくんないかなー」ってオタクとして思ってたんですけど、まさか...
As an otaku, I was thinking, "I wonder if she'll ever perform this?" But to think...
でもね、一緒に二人で歌ったことがなかったから歌ってみたくて。
But, you know, we've never sung together as a duo, so I really wanted to try it.
確かに。ホロハニだとね、結構ね、対やってること多いんですけどね。
Indeed. We're paired up quite a bit in HoloHoney and stuff, though.
フェスとかでも歌ったけど3人とかだったから、あのデュエットってやったことがなくて。
We've sung at festivals and such, but that was as a trio, so we've never done a duet.
確かに。
That's true.
ねえ。
Right?
ありがたいお話でございまして本当に。
I'm truly grateful for the opportunity.
いやいや、本当にこちらこそ。
No, no, the pleasure was all mine!
貴重な体験を。
Such a precious experience.
いや、こちらこそありがとうございました、本当に。
No, thank you so much, really!
ありがとうございました、本当に。
Thank you so very much.
はーい。
Alright.
Yes.
いや、それにしても、
Anyway,
はい。
Yes?
今日これ新衣装なんですよね。
this is a new outfit today, isn't it?
そうなんですよ。新衣装なんですよ。
That's right! It's my new outfit.
どう？
What do you think?
おー！
Wow!
いやちょっと、あのリオナさんがなんか結構際どいことやってたんですけど、
Well, Riona-san was doing something pretty daring earlier, but...
何？
What?
やはりね、あのー、やっぱちょっとこっちのぐいぐい隊オタクとして1個よろしいでしょうか？
as an assertive otaku, may I say just one thing?
何でしょう？
What is it?
やはり男というものはですね、やっぱあの、ひと肌脱いだ姿がすごい気になるというものでございまして、
Men are naturally very curious about seeing someone show a little skin,
あの、この隠されている純白が、あの、この姿が見れるのかっていうのがすごく気になっておりまして。ええ、あの本当に。
and I'm really curious if we'll ever get to see what's hidden underneath all this pure white. Yes, truly.
だってこの下のなんかもう清楚感溢れるこれ、絶対みんな気になるでしょ？
I mean, this piece underneath is overflowing with pure seiso vibes, so everyone's got to be curious, right?
いや、オタクとしてですね、もう気になりますよこんなの！
As an otaku, of course we're super curious about this!
そうですよね。
That makes sense.
はい。
Yes.
でも、この配信の中ではちょっとまだ見せれないかな〜
But I don't think I can show it just yet in this stream~
え？え、も、もしかして、そ、それは、それは脱げるということでござるか？
Huh? C-Could that mean... that it can actually be taken off, gozaru?!
この配信の中では見せることはないんだけどー
While I won't be showing it in this stream...
おっと？
Uh-oh?
ねえ。
Right?
メン限に入れ？メン限だったら見れるかもしれないと？
"Join the membership"? You're saying we might see it in a members-only stream?!
はい。いや、楽しみにしておりますので。
Yes! I'm really looking forward to it.
こちらこそ。
Me too!
メン限に入れ？入れ？メン限に入れ？すごい強制的（笑）
"Join the membership? Join? Join the membership?!" That's so pushy!
ぐいぐい…いやだって、こ、これが取れた姿が見れるんですよね？
So pushy... But I mean, we'll get to see what it looks like without this, right?
この後も楽しみにしてますよー！
I'll be looking forward to the rest of the stream!
はーい！
Okay!
というわけで、そら先輩まだこの後も全然続くと思うんですけど、
So, Sora-senpai, I'm sure you still have plenty more ahead,
はい。
Yes.
頑張ってください！
but please do your best!
頑張るよー！
I will!
あの、プロとしてお待ちしておりますんで。
I'll be waiting for you as a pro.
そうね。また後で。
Alright. See you later.
はい。プロとして…
Yes. As a pro...
プロとして。
As a pro.
あ、やばいプロの世界に引き込まれてしまう。ああープロの世界に引き込まれ…でもござるはね、商品だからあの、お尻は出さないで！
Ah, no, I'm getting dragged into the world of pros! But I'm merchandise, so don't show my butt!
ありがとう…ありがとう…未来で待ってる…未来で待っててくれ…
Thank you... Thank you... I'll be waiting in the future... Wait for me in the future...!
指なんだ（笑）
Just a thumb?
さあ、何、何をね、あの「また後で」ってどういうことなんでしょうかね？
Now then, what on earth did she mean by "see you later"?
はい。プロとして…何のプロなんでしょうか？
Yeah. "As a pro"... what kind of pro is she talking about?
気になる方、アフターライブに来てもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！
If you're curious, I'd be so happy if you came to check out the after-live!
さて、ちょっと待ってくださいね。いよいよ終盤戦です。
Now then, please hold on for a moment. We're finally entering the final stretch.
お水おいちい！
The water is delicious!
いよいよ終盤戦なんですけど、最後まで盛り上がっていってください！
We're finally in the home stretch, so keep the hype going until the very end!
もしかしたら…あの子が来ちゃうかもね！
Maybe... a certain someone might even show up!
聴いてください、「プレイ」！
Please listen: "Play"!
ちょけろ
Fool around,
fool around.
さぁ図に乗って
Come on, get cocky,
いい加減にしろ
"give me a break"—
やめらんないねぇ
I just can't stop, can I?
どうしようもねぇ
It's hopeless.
言い訳なら後で
If it's excuses you want,
考えてくれてやる
I'll come up with some for you later.
王道とかくだらねぇな毎回
The royal road is so pointless every time,
自意識過剰なやつ徘徊
overly self-conscious folks loitering around.
みんなが右往左往する間に
While everyone's rushing around in confusion,
こちとら地に足つけてきたぜハイハイ
we've kept our feet on the ground, yeah, yeah.
どうした？みんな
What's wrong? Why is everyone
浮かばない顔して
making such gloomy faces?
絵空事大歓迎よ
Fantasies and wild dreams are more than welcome!
diggin' dong ding
現実味ねぇよ
There's no realism here!
diggin' dong ding
早く楽になりたい？
Wanna take it easy soon?
いつでもいいよ
(Anytime is fine.)
おねんねさせたれ
Put 'em right to sleep!
nothing to do with you
ちょけろ
Fool around,
fool around.
さぁ図に乗って
Come on, get cocky,
いい加減にしろ
"give me a break"—
やめらんないねぇ
I just can't stop, can I?
爆ぜろ 爆ぜろ
Burst, burst!
おおー
Ohhh!
責任だって取るよ
I'll take responsibility,
墓場までは
all the way to the grave.
堂々とだけさせてくれよ
Just let me stand tall and proud!
こちとらマイペースなトラブルメーカー
I'm just a trouble maker going at my own pace.
とりあえず取扱説明書
For starters, read the user manual
隅から隅まで読んでおきな
from cover to cover!
ヒヤッとしたって何故か
Even when getting chills, somehow
ニヤッとしちゃうのおっかしいな
I end up grinning—how weird is that?
止めろ 止めろ 止めろ 止めろ
Stop it, stop it, stop it, stop it!
絵空事も大歓迎よ
Even fantasies and wild dreams are welcome!
diggin' dong ding
現実味ねぇよ
There's no realism here!
diggin' dong ding
早く楽になりたい？
Wanna take it easy soon?
いつでもいいよ
(Anytime is fine.)
おねんねさせたれ
Put 'em right to sleep!
nothing to do with you
押せよ
Press it,
そのリセットボタン
that reset button!
消せよ
Erase it,
お前のその価値観
those values of yours!
どうせ何度でも元に戻せるなら
If we can revert it back anytime anyway,
指咥えて見てるだけじゃつまらないやいや
just sucking our thumbs and watching is so boring!
あー！
Ah!
ah, so I'm ready
思いっきり前ノリ気味
leaning fully into the groove,
止まる気ないアクセルベタ踏み
no intention to stop, pedal to the metal!
ねぇ are you kidding?
Hey, are you kidding?
はいちょっと待ってここでストップ
Alright, hold on, stop right here!
return to the start
ぜってーやべーよ
This is definitely bad news!
話がちげーぞ
This isn't what we agreed on!
早く楽になりたい？
Wanna take it easy soon?
いつでもいいよ
(Anytime is fine.)
おねんねさせたれ
Put 'em right to sleep!
ナンセンス決定って言っちゃって
Call it all nonsense and decide,
押せよ そのリセットボタン
Press that reset button!
消せよ 前のその価値観
Erase those old values!
本当はもう二度と 戻ってこれないから
Because in truth, you can never go back again,
調子に乗せて寄せてみるのが 楽でいいのかもしれないな
Maybe just riding the wave and going with the flow is the easiest way.
はーい！ありがとうございました！
All right! Thank you so much!
この曲、『プレイ』を歌わせていただきました！
That was the song "Play"!
そして、この曲ではなんとサングラスをかけたあん肝がやってきました。
And for this song, Ankimo joined me wearing sunglasses!
どうじゃ、サングラス？
How do you like the sunglasses?
わー、取れたー！
Whoa, they came off!
あ、飛ばないのね、いい。
Ah, they're not flying off, good.
というわけで久々にね、あん肝と一緒になんか踊った気がするんだけど、どう？
So yeah, I feel like it's been a while since I danced with Ankimo like this. How was it?
5人目のゲスト、あん肝です！
Our fifth guest, it's Ankimo!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ある意味シークレットだったぜ。めっちゃ踊るやん！
In a way, he was a secret guest. Look at those dance moves!
そしてね、まあそんな感じで、
And so, moving on...
まだね、最後にね、実はお披露目もあるんだけど、ここでね、
We still have one final reveal coming up, but right now...
まず恒例のお知らせがたくさんあるので！
We have a lot of our usual announcements!
ここからはあん肝も一緒に告知していこうねー！聞いてください！
So Ankimo and I will go through the announcements together! Please take a look!
まずはこちら！
First up, this!
ときのそら誕生日記念2026グッズでーす！
It's the Tokino Sora Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise!
順番に紹介していくよー！
I'll introduce them one by one!
まずはこちら！
First is this one!
「Dream! そらとも法被」！
The "Dream! Soratomo Happi Coat"!
イラストはおるだん先生です！
Illustrated by Ordan-sensei!
テーマは「ライブをしてる私」ということで、なんとね、あん肝もいっぱいいるんだよ！ねっ！
The theme is "Me performing live," and look, there are lots of Ankimos too! Right?
今までもオリジナル法被自体はイベントやストアとかで出たことはあるんですけど、
While I've had original happi coats at events and stores before,
自分でオリジナルで作るのは初めてだったので、
this is the first time I made one as an original design myself,
ぜひライブで着てきてほしいなと思って作りました！
so I made it hoping you'd wear it to my concerts!
ぜひぜひみんな楽しんでくださいねー！
So please, everyone, enjoy wearing it!
ライブに着てきてくださーい！
Please wear it to my live shows!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
「お部屋でのんびり」ワイドラバーマット！
The "Relaxing in the Room" Wide Rubber Mat!
イェーイ！イラストはシワスタカシ先生です！
Yay! Illustrated by Takashi Shiwasu-sensei!
テーマは部屋でファンレターを読んでいる私で、
The theme is me reading fan letters in my room,
こちらね、ホロカのやつのね、ちょうどいいサイズになってるので、
and it's just the right size for playing the HoloKa card game,
ホロカを遊ぶ方、ぜひぜひ！
so if you play HoloKa, by all means!
一緒にね、持っていって遊んでもらえたら嬉しいなと思います！
I'd be really happy if you take it along and use it to play!
続いてはこちら！
Next is this!
「そらとおそろい スマホリング」！
The "Matching Smartphone Ring with Sora"!
前回販売したDJしょーパーカーとデザインが一緒なので、
It shares the same design as the DJ Show Hoodie sold previously,
それと一緒に合わせてスマホも私とおそろっち、みたいにしませんか？っていう感じです！
so how about pairing it up so your phone matches with me too? That's the idea!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up, we have this!
「そらザウルスなりきり そらちゃんぬいぐるみ」！
The "Sorazaurus Cosplay Sora-chan Plushie"!
みんなー！みんながあまりにもさ、「そらザウルス、そらザウルス」って言うからさ、
Everyone! You guys kept saying "Sorazaurus, Sorazaurus" so much,
でもそらザウルス自体をなんか言うのはちょっと恥ずかしかったから、
but I felt a bit embarrassed to make a plushie of Sorazaurus itself,
そらちゃんぬいぐるみ、私が着ていることにするなりきりぬいぐるみにしました！
so I made a plushie of me cosplaying in a Sorazaurus suit!
しかもね、「何、そらザウルスって？」って思う人、
And for anyone wondering, "What is Sorazaurus?",
これ取ると、フードが取れるともうピンクの衣装を着てる私みたいになるので、
if you remove the hood, it looks just like me in a pink outfit,
ぜひぜひフードを取り外して可愛く持ち歩いてくれてもいいんじゃないかなと思います！
so you can take off the hood and carry it around adorably!
そして最後はこちら！
And finally, this!
ASMRボイス！ボイスタイトル「届いてるよ、きみの応援」ということで、
An ASMR voice pack! Titled "I Hear It, Your Support,"
部屋でファンレターを読んでいるシチュエーションになっておりますので、
it's set in a scenario where I'm reading fan letters in my room,
ぜひぜひ皆さん、どんな風にファンレター読んでるのかなと想像しながら聴いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
so I hope you'll listen while imagining how I read your letters!
そしてフルセット購入特典はこちら！
And here is the bonus for purchasing the full set!
直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードと、特典ボイス！
A postcard with an authentic signature & foil-stamped message, plus a bonus voice!
ボイスタイトルは「誕生日を迎えて」になります！
The bonus voice title is "Welcoming My Birthday"!
というわけでですね、皆さん急がなくて大丈夫です！
So, you don't need to rush, everyone!
数量限定ではございませんので、皆さん全員分のサインを書かせていただきます！
This is not limited in quantity, so I will sign for every single one of you!
いくらでも書きますので、ぜひぜひ皆さん！
I'll write as many as it takes, so please, everyone!
たくさんの人にグッズを買ってもらえたら私はとても、そらち大喜び！なので、
If lots of people get the goods, Sorachi will be super thrilled!
よろしくお願いいたします！
Thank you for your support!
以上、ときのそら誕生日記念2026グッズでした！
That wraps up the Tokino Sora Birthday Celebration 2026 merchandise!
みんなよろしくねー！
Check them out, everyone!
続いてのお知らせはこちら！
The next announcement is this!
多いので駆け足で！
There's a lot, so I'll go through quickly!
11月ワンマンライブの「ときのそら 生誕記念 先行チケット販売開始」ということで、
For my solo live in November, early ticket sales for "Tokino Sora Birthday Commemoration" have begun!
ぴあアリーナの先行チケットが本日から始まっております！
Early ticket applications for Pia Arena MM have started today!
ぴあアリーナ、ファンクラブに入ってる人しかできないんじゃないかって言ってた人！
For anyone thinking only fan club members could apply,
本日から一般で皆さんも販売が開始されておりますので、
general presales are open to everyone starting today!
ぜひぜひ！もう12時から開始されております！
So please do! Applications opened at 12:00 PM today!
応募していただけたら嬉しいです！
I'd love it if you applied!
みんなでぴあアリーナでライブ楽しもう！
Let's enjoy the live concert together at Pia Arena!
さらにこちら！
And furthermore, this!
現地チケットの特典でもらえるホロカのお披露目、これももうお披露目でございました！
Here is the reveal of the HoloKa card included as an on-site ticket perk!
ライブの来場者特典として限定ホロカが1枚配られます。
As a venue visitor bonus, one exclusive HoloKa card will be handed out.
全2種類のうち1枚をランダムでお渡しするのですが、そちらの1枚を公開です！
You'll receive one random card out of two types, and here is a look at one of them!
私が描き下ろすということで、もう1個の方はまだなので、
I drew this illustration myself! The other one isn't ready yet, so...
ぜひこちらの方で、ちょっと...
Please check this out and... hehe,
えー、満足していただけないでしょうか？
won't you be satisfied with this?
そして、9周年ライブを記念して、こちら！
And to commemorate the 9th anniversary live, look at this!
えー、スペシャルテレビCM放送決定！ということで、
A special 60-second TV commercial broadcast has been confirmed!
え、本日の22時半から23時の間で、
Today, between 22:30 and 23:00,
え、TOKYO MXさんのところで流れます。
it will air on TOKYO MX.
1度だけなので、ぜひ見てくれると嬉しいなと思いますよ。
It will only air once, so I'd love it if you checked it out.
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
そしてそして、最後のお知らせが、こちら！
And next, the final announcement is this!
お待たせしました！
Thank you for waiting!
こちらです！新曲『決意のソラへ』です！
Here it is! A new song, "Ketsui no Sora e"!
えー、私的には、なんかエモい感じの曲とかね、泣き曲かなって思ったんだけど、
Personally, I thought it might be an emotional tearjerker,
でもディレクターさん的にはもう泣き曲とかエモとかそういう感じじゃない、熱い曲みたいな感じで、
but the director said it's not just emotional or tearful, but an intense, passionate track,
オープニングに相応しい感じのくらいの熱い曲を作ったつもり、みたいなこと言っていたので、
and that they intended to make a fiery song truly fitting for an opening theme.
この後ね、MVがプレミア公開も予定されているので、各種音楽サイトでも配信もされています。
Right after this, the MV premiere is scheduled, and it's also out on various streaming platforms.
ぜひたくさん聴いてもらえたら嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if you gave it lots of listens!
はい、というわけでね、とっても楽しかったんですけど、いかがだったでしょうか？
Alright! So, it was so much fun, but how did you like it?
告知がね、あの洪水のやってきたと思うので、
A whole flood of announcements came your way,
後でみんな確認してもらえると嬉しいなと思います。
so I hope everyone checks them all out later!
えー、そしてですね、メン限は21時半から、えー、アフターライブがあるんですけど、
And also, starting at 21:30 for members only, we'll have an after-live stream,
えー、スペシャルあん肝がね、なんとね、見れるかもしれないんだって。スペシャルだよ。スペシャル。
and you might just get to see a special Anmou! It's special! Special!
もう、このサングラスあん肝もスペシャルではあるんだけど、
Even though sunglasses Anmou is already special,
さらにスペシャルなあん肝が見れるかもしれない。
you might see an even more special Anmou.
そしてね、さっきも言いました、この... この放送では、
And as I mentioned earlier, during this broadcast,
まぁ、ちょっとまだ脱げないかな？って言ってたもの、ありますよね。
there's something I said I couldn't take off just yet, right?
色んな撮影会しましょう！
Let's do all sorts of photo shoots!
というわけで、ここまで付き合ってくれてありがとう！あん肝、バイバイ！
So, thank you for sticking with me till now! Anmou, bye-bye!
サングラス、似合ってたぞ！
Those sunglasses looked good on you!
みんな吸い込まれていく。
Everyone's getting sucked in.
はい、というわけでね、皆さん、いかがだったでしょうか？
Alright, everyone, how was the stream?
そんなこんなで、こんなにね、いつもの情報の洪水が起こっていると思うんですが、
Just like that, there was the usual flood of info,
ぜひぜひ皆さん後で見てもらえたら嬉しいです。
but I'd really appreciate it if you all check it out later.
えー、最後はですね、こんだけ『決意のソラへ』と言っておいて歌わないのはどうかなと思いますので、
Lastly, after talking so much about "Ketsui no Sora e," it wouldn't feel right not to sing it,
新曲で締めたいと思います！
so I'd like to close with my new song!
それでは聴いてください、『決意のソラへ』！
Please listen to "Ketsui no Sora e"!
一度きりの 私の物語には
In this once-in-a-lifetime story of mine,
運命を 超えて
transcending destiny,
きらめくんだ
I will shine!
行こう
Let's go!
みんな本日はありがとうございます！とっても楽しかったー！
Thank you all so much for today! I had so much fun!
ねえ 私より 私のことを
Hey, having you by my side, who understands me
分かってくれる 君の存在が
even better than I know myself,
臆病で泣き虫な心に
cast a magic spell called courage
勇気という魔法をかけただろう
onto my timid, crybaby heart.
チクタク 時計の針だけが進む
Tick-tock, only the clock hands move forward;
立ち止まってちゃダメだ
I can't just stand still.
それ 転びようがお決まりでしょう
Tripping over is just par for the course, right?
ひとつ ひとつ 重ねてきた
One by one, as if flipping through
大切な アルバムをめくるように
a precious album of memories,
ひとつ ひとつ 叶えてきた 今日まで
one by one, we made dreams come true until today,
その全てに 君がいてくれた
and you were there through every single part of it.
終わりのない 夢を
This endless dream,
ずっと ずっと ずっと ずっと 追いかけていこう
forever and ever, always and always, let's keep chasing it!
行こう
Let's go!
Xのトレンド入りも果たしたそうで、ありがとうございます！
I heard we're trending on X, thank you all so much!
ねえ ここって 笑い合えることが
Hey, being able to laugh together here
何よりも大事な真実
is the most important truth of all.
チクチク 悪戯なハートが痛む
Prick-prick, my mischievous heart aches,
から回りに空回り 深呼吸
spinning round and round, take a deep breath;
色塗り替えて ねえ夜空
repainting the colors, hey, night sky!
泣いて 泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even the nights I cried and cried and cried,
大切な 人生のストーリーだから
are a precious part of my life's story, so...
夢を夢で終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want to let my dreams end as just dreams.
まだ見ぬ景色を見に行こうよ
Let's go see the sights we haven't seen yet.
もっともっと (もっともっと)
More and more (More and more)
輝いて (輝いて)
Shining bright (Shining bright)
高く高く (高く高く)
Higher and higher (Higher and higher)
飛び立とう
Let's take flight,
奇跡さえも超えて
and surpass even miracles!
はい！はい！はい！はい！
Hai! Hai! Hai! Hai!
皆さんたくさんのコメント、ありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much for all your comments!
ひとつ ひとつ 重ねてきた
Page by page, we've layered them together,
未来地図のページをめくるように
as if turning the pages of our map of the future.
泣いて 泣いて 泣いた夜も
Even those nights when I cried and cried,
大切な人生のストーリーだから
are all precious parts of my life's story.
夢を夢で終わらせたくないんだ
I don't want to let my dreams end as just dreams.
まだ見ぬ景色を見に行こうよ
Let's go see the sights we haven't seen yet.
終わりのない歌を
An endless song,
君に 君に 君へと届け
reach you, reach you, reach all the way to you!
ずっと ずっと 誓うの 決意のソラへ
Forever and always, I vow—towards the sky of determination,
行こう！
let's go!
本当にみんなのおかげで、最高の誕生日になりました！
Thanks to all of you, this has been the best birthday ever!
みんなのこと、大好きだよ！
I love you all so much!
アフターライブも来てね！
Make sure to come to the after-live too!
ばいばーい！
Bye-bye!
それではライブ配信を終了します。配信終了。
We will now end the live stream. Stream ended.